[{"answer": "Boy band", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Boy band", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "...my friend, you are the sweet one. Will you please just cooperate and no", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "You can't be the tough one, because you're Jewish", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "I wanna be the tough one", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Jews are tough", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Alright, guys, here we go.  Hello, sir", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "We... are Fingerbang", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend. So, can we play here", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "No?", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "What?? ...No", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Who?? No", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Well uh, uh, oh... Right now there's a cheese and sausage cart in the plaza. And I would uh, I'd hate to have to move it off to the side for a while. What", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No. I mean, you're just not as good as sausage and cheese", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "No. I mean, you're just not as good as sausage and cheese", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Wow. That was your best", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What?! I specifically told him not to do that", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "And what if they do make it, my friend?! What if they DO make itare YOU gonna be the one to tell 'im?", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Alright, my friend, what's the matter", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Well, my friend, I, I think you were just focusin' in on the wrong thing. Boy bands aren't about music, Boy bands are created by corporations to make money. They're all based on the Gomlich effect", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Because I said so", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Let 'em be pissed off, then", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Wew. There must be at least 20 people out there", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "He'll be here. my friend wouldn't douche", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "You bastards", "docId": "South-Park-Something-You-Can-Do-With-Your-Finger.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Dude, he's pretty dead", "qsentId": 26}]